

System Analyst specializing in development and supports of Oracle PeopleSoft. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic ERP and ETL projects. Well-versed in programming languages including PeopleCode, SQL, PL/SQL. Strong background in ERP, ETL systems project management, development and inhouse supports in banking industry.

Lawrence, Chi Man Law

Phone:

+852 94012991

E-Mail:

lawrencelaw12@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chi-man-law-93730016b/

Skill Highlights

- Programming
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Fast learner

Languages

English – Fluent Chinese – Fluent

Experience

09/2010 to now

System Analyst - The Bank of East Asia, Hong Kong

- Work and coordinate with IT infrastructure team, vendor and user to implement projects
- Support for application configuration setup, including Oracle, Unix and Windows
- Gather and analyze user requirements, lead and communicate with team members to implement system program changes raised by user requests/system issues
- Provide support on Production issue, UAT cycle run, DR drill and SDLC documentations.
- Improve and optimize program performance and production batch flow
- Completed projects
 - ✓ Budget and forecasting system implementation project (Oracle Hyperion)
 - ✓ Peoplesoft Peopletool upgrade project for FSCM
 - ✓ IFRS9 implementation project (Moody's Analytics Risk Confidence)
 - ✓ Basel BCBS239 standard implementation project
 - ✓ Oracle Peoplesoft FSCM 8.8 to 9.2 upgrade project

09/2008 to 9/2010

Technical Consultant - iTech Consulting Services Limited

- Develops reports for Workforce, Absence Management and Payroll modules in PeopleSoft HRMS
- Responsible for customization across diverse modules in PeopleSoft Campus Solutions including student records, students finance and student accounts interfacing
- Participated in 4 Oracle Peoplesoft HRMS implementation projects and 1 Campus Solution implementation project

Education

2005-2008

Bachelor of Science: Enterprise Information Systems-The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, Hong Kong